{
    "subject": "resource/Scooby-Doo!_Pirates_Ahoy!",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "Scooby-Doo!'s country of origin is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9669151902198792,
            "question": "Which country is associated with the origin of Scooby-Doo!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9132221937179565,
            "question": "From which country does Scooby-Doo! originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8614949584007263,
            "question": "Can Scooby-Doo!'s origins be traced to a specific country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7350486516952515,
            "question": "Is Scooby-Doo! an American production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5817450284957886,
            "question": "What nationality are the creators of Scooby-Doo!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5789818167686462,
            "question": "What country is the home of Scooby-Doo!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.554970383644104,
            "question": "Where was Scooby-Doo! created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3992845118045807,
            "question": "Is Scooby-Doo! a product of American animation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31992125511169434,
            "question": "Where are the characters in Scooby-Doo! from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07186836004257202,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the show's creators?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Scooby-Doo!'s country of origin is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5247_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are the characters in Scooby-Doo! from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5247_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Scooby-Doo! a product of American animation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5247_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Scooby-Doo! created?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5247_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5247_74.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Scooby-Doo! originated from the United States. The document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5247/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt` mentions that Scooby-Doo was born on 1962 in Dooville, United States, which implies that he originated from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The context information provided mentions that Scooby-Doo was created in the United States by American animation company Hanna-Barbera. This supports the claim that the country of origin for the character is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}